<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PhotoMendy, The Journal</title>
    <link>http://static.phatbloke.lan/</link>
    <description>Recent content on PhotoMendy, The Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 09:46:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://static.phatbloke.lan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Show Must Go On</title>
      <link>http://static.phatbloke.lan/posts/the-show-must-go-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 09:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://static.phatbloke.lan/posts/the-show-must-go-on/</guid>
      <description>After a very good nights sleep I am over the man flu. Despite this I am still not feeling the best, I blame Putin. Not joking, just as the world is looking like it&amp;rsquo;s over the worse of Covid, Putin invades Ukraine. I doubt I am alone in being scared of what this might escalate to and we already know many are going to suffer as energy prices soar. This may lead to the economy suffering as people have less to spend in order to pay those energy bills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Struggling</title>
      <link>http://static.phatbloke.lan/posts/struggling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 08:51:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://static.phatbloke.lan/posts/struggling/</guid>
      <description>Struggling is to be expected, especially if you are feeling unwell. I&amp;rsquo;m struggling right now, little has been done since Day 1 due to feeling unwell. I was sleep deprived and then I got man flu. I did a Covid test, at least it was not that. Yesterday I was feeling so unwell, I went to bed at 5pm. I was restless and got up a couple of times before finally getting to sleep around 11pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journey begins</title>
      <link>http://static.phatbloke.lan/posts/journey-begins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 17:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://static.phatbloke.lan/posts/journey-begins/</guid>
      <description>The journey begins. Welcome to my my first entry in this journal. As of writing, this idea was born a month or two ago. Simple idea, provide image editing services for anyone who needs it. Photographers, artists and entrepreneurs are the first type of people I have thought of and I feel there are probably many other industries that may benefit from such services.
My approach is to start with something simple and to make a little pocket money to start with and later turn into something I can earn a living with.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
